<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<elements>
	<info>
		<name>War priest</name>
		<description>The War priest class by Lycane.</description>
		<update version="0.3.3">
			<file name="Warpriest" url="" />
		</update>
	</info>

	<element name="War Priest" type="Class" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_LYCANE_WAR_PRIEST">
		<description>
            <p>War has many manifestations. It can make heroes of ordinary people. It can be desperate and horrific, with acts of cruelty and cowardice eclipsing instances of excellence and courage. In either case, the gods of war watch over warriors and reward them for their great deeds. The clerics of such gods excel in battle, inspiring others to fight the good fight or offering acts of violence as prayers. Gods of war include champions of honor and chivalry (such as Torm, Heironeous, and Kiri- Jolith) as well as gods of destruction and pillage (such as Erythnul, the Fury, Gruumsh, and Ares) and gods of conquest and domination (such as Bane, Hextor, and Maglubiyet). Other war gods (such as Tempus, Nike, and Nuada) take a more neutral stance, promoting war in all its manifestations and supporting warriors in any circumstance.</p>
			<!-- buradan aşağısı editlenecek-->
			<p class="indent">A dwarf crouches behind an outcrop, his black cloak making him nearly invisible in the night, and watches an orc war band celebrating its recent victory. Silently, he stalks into their midst and whispers an oath, and two orcs are dead before they even realize he is there.</p>
			<p class="indent">Silver hair shining in a shaft of light that seems to illuminate only him, an elf laughs with exultation. His spear flashes like his eyes as he jabs again and again at a twisted giant, until at last his light overcomes its hideous darkness.</p>
			<p class="indent">Whatever their origin and their mission, War Priests are united by their oaths to stand against the forces of evil. Whether sworn before a god’s altar and the witness of a priest, in a sacred glade before nature spirits and fey beings, or in a moment of desperation and grief with the dead as the only witness, a War Priest’s oath is a powerful bond. It is a source of power that turns a devout warrior into a blessed champion.</p>
			<h4>THE CAUSE OF RIGHTEOUSNESS</h4>
			<p>A War Priest swears to uphold justice and righteousness, to stand with the good things of the world against the encroaching darkness, and to hunt the forces of evil wherever they lurk. Different War Priests focus on various aspects of the cause of righteousness, but all are bound by the oaths that grant them power to do their sacred work. Although many War Priests are devoted to gods of good, a War Priest’s power comes as much from a commitment to justice itself as it does from a god. War Priests train for years to learn the skills of combat, mastering a variety of weapons and armor. Even so, their martial skills are secondary to the magical power they wield: power to heal the sick and injured, to smite the wicked and the undead, and to protect the innocent and those who join them in the fight for justice.</p>
			<h4>BEYOND THE MUNDANE LIFE</h4>
			<p>Almost by definition, the life of a War Priest is an adventuring life. Unless a lasting injury has taken him or her away from adventuring for a time, every War Priest lives on the front lines of the cosmic struggle against evil. Fighters are rare enough among the ranks of the militias and armies of the world, but even fewer people can claim the true calling of a War Priest. When they do receive the call, these warriors turn from their former occupations and take up arms to fight evil. Sometimes their oaths lead them into the service of the crown as leaders of elite groups of knights, but even then their loyalty is first to the cause of righteousness, not to crown and country.</p>
			<p class="indent">Adventuring War Priests take their work seriously. A delve into an ancient ruin or dusty crypt can be a quest driven by a higher purpose than the acquisition of treasure. Evil lurks in dungeons and primeval forests, and even the smallest victory against it can tilt the cosmic balance away from oblivion.</p>
			<h4>CREATING A War Priest</h4>
			<p>The most important aspect of a War Priest character is the nature of his or her holy quest. Although the class features related to your oath don't appear until you reach 3rd level, plan ahead for that choice by reading the oath descriptions at the end of the class. Are you a devoted servant of good, loyal to the gods of justice and honor, a holy knight in shining armor venturing forth to smite evil? A re you a glorious champion of the light, cherishing everything beautiful that stands against the shadow, a knight whose oath descends from traditions older than many of the gods? Or are you an embittered loner sworn to take vengeance on those who have done great evil, sent as an angel of death by the gods or driven by your need for revenge? Appendix B lists many deities worshiped by War Priests throughout the multiverse, such as Torm, Tyr, Heironeous, War Prieste, Kiri-Jolith, Dol Arrah, the Silver Flame, Bahamut, Athena, Re-Horakhty, and Heimdall.</p>
			<p class="indent">How did you experience your call to serve as a War Priest? Did you hear a whisper from an unseen god or angel while you were at prayer? Did another War Priest sense the potential within you and decide to train you as a squire? Or did some terrible event—the destruction of your home, perhaps— drive you to your quests? Perhaps you stumbled into a sacred grove or a hidden elven enclave and found yourself called to protect all such refuges of goodness and beauty. Or you might have known from your earliest memories that the War Priest’s life was your calling, almost as if you had been sent into the world with that purpose stamped on your soul.</p>
			<p class="indent">As guardians against the forces of wickedness, War Priests are rarely of any evil alignment. Most of them walk the paths of charity and justice. Consider how your alignment colors the way you pursue your holy quest and the manner in which you conduct yourself before gods and mortals. Your oath and alignment might be in harmony, or your oath might represent standards of behavior that you have not yet attained.</p>
			<h5>QUICK BUILD</h5>
			<p>You can make a War Priest quickly by following these suggestions. First, Strength should be your highest ability score, followed by Charisma. Second, choose the noble background.</p>
			<h3>CLASS FEATURES</h3>
			<p>As a War Priest, you gain the following class features.</p>
            <h5>HIT POINTS</h5>
            <ul class="unstyled">
                <li><strong>Hit Dice:</strong> 1d10 per War Priest level</li>
                <li><strong>Hit Points at 1st Level:</strong> 10 + your Constitution modifier</li>
                <li><strong>Hit Points at Higher Levels:</strong> 1d10 (or 6) + your Constitution modifier per War Priest level after 1st</li>
            </ul>
            <h5>PROFICIENCIES</h5>
            <ul class="unstyled mb">
                <li><strong>Armor:</strong> All armor, shields</li>
                <li><strong>Weapons:</strong> Simple weapons, martial weapons</li>
                <li><strong>Tools:</strong> None</li>
            </ul>
            <ul class="unstyled">
                <li><strong>Saving Throws:</strong> Wisdom, Charisma</li>
                <li><strong>Skills:</strong> Choose two skills from Athletics, Insight, Intimidation, Medicine, Persuasion, and Religion</li>
            </ul>
			<h5>EQUIPMENT</h5>
			<p>You start with the following equipment, in addition to the equipment granted by your background:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><i>(a)</i> a martial weapon and a shield or <i>(b)</i> two martial weapons</li>
				<li><i>(a)</i> five javelins or <i>(b)</i> any simple melee weapon</li>
				<li><i>(a)</i> a priest’s pack or <i>(b)</i> an explorer’s pack</li>
				<li>Chain mail and a holy symbol</li>
			</ul>
			<h5 class="caption">THE War Priest</h5>
			<table class="class-features">
				<thead>
					<tr><td class="col-5">Level</td><td class="col-60 left">Features</td> 					<td>1st</td><td>2nd</td><td>3rd</td><td>4th</td><td>5th</td></tr>
				</thead>
				<tr><td> 1st</td><td class="left">Divine Sense,divine favor</td> 							<td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 2nd</td><td class="left">Fighting Style, Spellcasting</td> 						<td>2</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 3rd</td><td class="left">Divine Health, Divine Shield</td> 						<td>3</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 4th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement,Divine Word</td> 				<td>3</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 5th</td><td class="left">Blessing of the Temple</td> 								<td>4</td><td>2</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 6th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement,Aura of Protection</td> 		<td>4</td><td>2</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 7th</td><td class="left">Lead the War,spirit guardians</td> 						<td>4</td><td>3</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 8th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement,Divine Word Improvement</td> 	<td>4</td><td>3</td><td>—</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td> 9th</td><td class="left">Blessing of the War God</td> 								<td>4</td><td>3</td><td>2</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>10th</td><td class="left">Crusader’s mantle</td> 									<td>4</td><td>3</td><td>2</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>11th</td><td class="left">Flame strike</td> 										<td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>12th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement,Divine Word Improvement</td> 	<td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>—</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<!-- Buradan Aşağısı düzenlenecek-->
				<tr><td>13th</td><td class="left">—													</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>1</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>14th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement,Cleansing Touch			</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>1</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>15th</td><td class="left">Sacred Oath feature</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>2</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>16th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>2</td><td>—</td></tr>
				<tr><td>17th</td><td class="left">—</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>1</td></tr>
				<tr><td>18th</td><td class="left">Aura improvements</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>1</td></tr>
				<tr><td>19th</td><td class="left">Ability Score Improvement</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>2</td></tr>
				<tr><td>20th</td><td class="left">Sacred Oath feature</td><td>4</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>3</td><td>2</td></tr>
				<!-- Yukarısı düzenlenecek -->
			</table>
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_CLERIC_CHANNELDIVINITY" />
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_CLERIC_CHANNELDIVINITY_TURN_UNDEAD" />
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_FIGHTING_STYLE" />
			<div element="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_SPELLCASTING" />
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_DIVINE_HEALTH" />
			<div element="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_ASI" />
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_AURA_OF_PROTECTION" />
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_CLEANSING_TOUCH" />
			<div element="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_DOMAIN_AVATAR_OF_BATTLE" />
			<div element="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_BLESSING_OF_THE_WAR_GOD"/>
			<div element="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_DOUBLE_CONCENTRATION"/>

		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>The gods of war watch over warriors and reward them for their great deeds.</description>
		</sheet>
        <setters>
			<set name="short">The gods of war watch over warriors and reward them for their great deeds.</set>
			<set name="hd">d10</set>
		</setters>
		<rules>
            
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_ARMOR_PROFICIENCY_LIGHT_ARMOR" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_ARMOR_PROFICIENCY_MEDIUM_ARMOR" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_ARMOR_PROFICIENCY_HEAVY_ARMOR" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_ARMOR_PROFICIENCY_SHIELDS" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_WEAPON_PROFICIENCY_SIMPLE_WEAPONS" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_WEAPON_PROFICIENCY_MARTIAL_WEAPONS" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_SAVINGTHROW_WISDOM" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
            <grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_PROFICIENCY_SAVINGTHROW_CONSTITUTION" requirements="!ID_WOTC_PHB_MULTICLASS_PALADIN" />
			<select type="Proficiency" name="Skill Proficiency (War Priest)" supports="Skill"  number="4"/>

			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_DIVINE_FAVOR" level="1" spellcasting="War Priest" prepared="true" />
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_CRUSADERS_MANTLE" level="5" spellcasting="War Priest" prepared="true" />
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_SPIRIT_GUARDIANS" level="5" spellcasting="War Priest" prepared="true" />
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_PHB_SPELL_FLAME_STRIKE" level="9" spellcasting="War Priest" prepared="true" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_LANGUAGE" level="1" />
            <grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_LAY_ON_HANDS" level="1" />
            <grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_FIGHTING_STYLE" level="2" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_CLERIC_CHANNELDIVINITY" level="2" />
            <grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_SPELLCASTING" level="2" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_DIVINE_HEALTH" level="3" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_CASTING" level="2"/>
			<grant type="Class Featyre" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_DIVINE_WORDS_CASTING" level="4"/>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_ASI" level="4" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_DIVINE_WORD" level="4"/> 
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_PUSH_THE_LIMITS" level="4"/>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_BLESSING_OF_THE_TEMPLE" level="5"/>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_BLESSING_OF_THE_WAR_GOD" level="5"/>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_DOUBLE_CONCENTRATION" level="6"/>
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_AURA_OF_PROTECTION" level="6" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_CLEANSING_TOUCH" level="14" />
			<grant type="Class Feature" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_DOMAIN_AVATAR_OF_BATTLE" level="17"/>
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Triple Concentration" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_DOUBLE_CONCENTRATION">
		<sheet>
			<description>
				<p>War Priests possess the rare ability to concentrate on two tasks at once ,a rare ability whispered to originate from the gods themselves.</p>
			</description>
		</sheet>		
		</element>
	<element name="Language" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_LANGUAGE">
		<sheet display="false"/>
		<compendium display="false" />
		<rules>
			<select type="Language" name="Language (War Priest)" supports="Standard||Exotic" />
		</rules>		
		</element>
	<element name="Spellcasting" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_SPELLCASTING">
		<description>
			<p>By 2nd level, you have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric/War Priest does.</p>
			<h5>PREPARING AND CASTING SPELLS</h5>
			<p>The War Priest table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your war priest spells. To cast one of your war priest spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a slot of the spell’s level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
			<p class="indent">You prepare the list of war priest spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the War Priest spell list. When you do so, choose a number of war priest spells equal to your Wisdom modifier + half your war priest level, rounded down (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
			<p class="indent">You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of War Priest spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
			<h5>SPELLCASTING ABILITY</h5>
			<p>Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your War Priest spells, since their power derives from the strength of your convictions. You use your Wisdom whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a war priest spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
			<center>
				<p><strong>Spell save DC</strong> = 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</p>
				<p><strong>Spell attack modifier</strong> = your proficiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier</p>
			</center>
			<h5>SPELLCASTING FOCUS</h5>
			<p>You can use a weapon such as hammer as a spellcasting focus for your war priest spells.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false">
			<description>You have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric/paladin does.</description>
		</sheet>
		<spellcasting name="War Priest" ability="Wisdom" prepare="true">
			<list known="true">Cleric</list>
		</spellcasting>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Grants" id="ID_INTERNAL_RITUAL_CASTING" />
			<grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_INTERNAL_PROFICIENCY_SPELLFOCUS_GROUP_HOLY_SYMBOL" />

			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:1" value="2" level="2" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="3" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="5" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:2" value="2" level="5" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:2" value="1" level="7" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:3" value="2" level="9" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:3" value="1" level="11" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:4" value="1" level="13" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:4" value="1" level="15" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:4" value="1" level="17" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:5" value="1" level="17" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:slots:5" value="1" level="19" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:prepare" value="wisdom:modifier" />
			<stat name="war priest:spellcasting:prepare" value="level:war priest" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<!-- Bitti --><element name="Channel Divinity" type="Class Feature" source="Player’s Handbook" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_CLERIC_CHANNELDIVINITY">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_CHANNEL_DIVINITY</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 2nd level, you gain the ability to channel divine energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some domains grant you additional effects as you advance in levels, as noted in the domain description.</p>
			<p class="indent">When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.</p>
			<p class="indent">Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your cleric spell save DC.</p>
			<p class="indent">Beginning at 6th level, you can use your Channel Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at 18th level, you can use it three times between rests. When you finish a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.</p>
			<div element="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TURN_UNDEAD" />
			<div element="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_DIVINE_SHIELD" />
			<div element="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TAUNT"/>
			<div element="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_ZEN_HARMONY"/>
			<div element="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_DIVINE_INSIGHT" />
			<div element="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_DIVINE_COMMAND"/>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="{{channel divinity:count}}/Short Rest" />
		<rules>
			<stat name="channel divinity:count" value="1" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="channel divinity:count" value="2" level="6" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="channel divinity:count" value="3" level="8" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="channel divinity:count" value="4" level="12" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="channel divinity:count" value="5" level="15" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="channel divinity:count" value="6" level="18" bonus="base" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Channel Divinty" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_CASTING">
		<spellcasting name="Channel Divinity" ability="Wisdom" prepare="false"></spellcasting>
		<rules>
			<grant type="Grants" id="ID_INTERNAL_RITUAL_CASTING" />
			<grant type="Proficiency" id="ID_INTERNAL_PROFICIENCY_SPELLFOCUS_GROUP_HOLY_SYMBOL" />

			<stat name="Channel Divinity:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="2"/>
			<stat name="Channel Divinity:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="6"/>
			<stat name="Channel Divinity:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="9"/>
			<stat name="Channel Divinity:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="12"/>
			<stat name="Channel Divinity:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="15"/>
			<stat name="Channel Divinity:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="18"/>


			<grant type="Channel Divinity" id="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TURN_UNDEAD" level ="2" spellcasting="Channel Divinity" />
			<grant type="Channel Divinity" id="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_DIVINE_SHIELD" level="2" spellcasting="Channel Divinity" />
			<grant type="Channel Divinity" id="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_TAUNT" level="3" spellcasting="Channel Divinity" />
			<grant type="Channel Divinity" id="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_ZEN_HARMONY" level="5" spellcasting="Channel Divinity"/>
			<grant type="Channel Divinity" id="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_DIVINE_INSIGHT" level="6" spellcasting="Channel Divinity"/>
			<grant type="Channel Divinity" id="ID_CHANNEL_DIVINITY_DIVINE_COMMAND" level="7" spellcasting="Channel Divinity"/>
		</rules>
		<sheet display="false"></sheet>
	</element>

	<element name="Blessing of the Temple" type="Class Feature" source="The War priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_BLESSING_OF_THE_TEMPLE">
        <sheet>
			<description>
				<p>The Goddess of War and Hunt bestows her blessings upon her holy warriors, empowering them to remain steadfast on the battlefield. You gain an extra an AC and 10 HP.</p>
			</description>
		</sheet>
        <rules>
            <stat name="ac" value="1" />
			<stat name="hp" value="10"/>
        </rules>
    </element>

	
	<!-- Bitti --><element name="Push the Limits" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_PUSH_THE_LIMITS">
		<sheet>
			<description>
				<p>The gods bestow upon you the privilege to augment your divine word with their divine powers once a day. The Wisdom saving throw required of your opponents becomes more challenging, and the divine energy also impacts your mortal body. Your proficiency bonus is doubled for that saving throw.</p>
			</description>
		</sheet>		
	</element>

	
	<!-- Bitti --><element name="Divine Word" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_DIVINE_WORD">
		<description>
			<p>At 4th level, you gain the ability to speak divine words directly from your holy book, using that energy to command creatures.</p>
			<p class="indent">When you speak your Divine Words, you choose which effect to create. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.</p>
			<p class="indent">Some Divine Word effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your War Priest spell save DC.</p>
			<p class="indent">Beginning at 6th level and every 2 levels, you can speak your Divine Words once more between rests.When you finish a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.</p>
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_PARALYZE(INFIGE IMMOBILITATEM)" />
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_SILENCE(SILENTIUM)"/>
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_HEAL(CONFERVO)"/>
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_TERRORIZE(TERROREM INSTILLA)"/>
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_PAIN(TORMENTUM)"/>
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_CONFESS(CONFESSIONEM EVOCA)" />
			<div element="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_IMPRISON(CAPTIVARE)"/>
		</description>
		<sheet usage="{{divine word:count}}/Short Rest" />
		<rules>
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="1" level="4" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="2" level="6" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="3" level="8" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="4" level="10" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="5" level="12" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="6" level="14" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="7" level="16" bonus="base" />
			<stat name="divine word:count" value="8" level="18" bonus="base" />

		</rules>
	</element>
	
	<element name="Divine Words" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_DIVINE_WORDS_CASTING">
		<spellcasting name="Divine Word" ability="Wisdom" prepare="true">
			<list>War Priest</list>
		</spellcasting>
		<rules>

			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="4"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="6"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="8"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="10"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="12"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="14"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="16"/>
			<stat name="Divine Word:spellcasting:slots:1" value="1" level="18"/>


			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_PARALYZE(INFIGE IMMOBILITATEM)" level="4" spellcasting="Divine Word"/>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_SILENCE(SILENTIUM)" level="4" spellcasting="Divine Word" />
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_TERRORIZE(TERROREM INSTILLA)" level="4" spellcasting="Divine Word"/>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_IMPRISON(CAPTIVARE)" level="4" spellcasting="Divine Word" />
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_HEAL(CONFERVO)" level="8" spellcasting="Divine Word"/>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_CONFESS(CONFESSIONEM EVOCA)" level="8" spellcasting="Divine Word"/>
			<grant type="Spell" id="ID_SPELL_DIVINE_WORD_PAIN(TORMENTUM)" level="12" spellcasting="Divine Word"/>
		</rules>
		<sheet display="false"></sheet>
	</element>

	
	
	<element name="Lay on Hands" type="Class Feature" source="Player’s Handbook" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_PALADIN_LAY_ON_HANDS">
		<description>
			<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your War Priest level x 5.</p>
			<p class="indent">As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
			<p class="indent">Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
			<p class="indent">This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet action="Action" usage="{{lay on hands:hp pool}}/Long Rest" >
			<description>You can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hp to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool. 
			You can expend 5 hp from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it.
			This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<stat name="lay on hands:hp pool" value="level:war priest" />
			<stat name="lay on hands:hp pool" value="level:war priest" />
			<stat name="lay on hands:hp pool" value="level:war priest" />
			<stat name="lay on hands:hp pool" value="level:war priest" />
			<stat name="lay on hands:hp pool" value="level:war priest" />
		</rules>
	</element>
		<element name="Ability Score Improvement" type="Class Feature" source="Player’s Handbook" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_ASI">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_PALADIN_ABILITY_SCORE_IMPROVEMENT</requirements>
		<compendium display="false" />
		<description>
			<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can’t increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet display="false" />
		<rules>
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 4)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,4" level="4" />
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 6)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,6" level="6" />
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 8)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,8" level="8" />
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 12)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,12" level="12" />
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 14)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,14" level="14" />
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 16)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,16" level="16" />
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Improvement Option (War Priest 19)" supports="Improvement Option,Paladin,19" level="19" />
		</rules>
	</element>

	<element name="Blessing of the War God" type="Class Feature" source="The War Priest by Lycane" id="ID_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_PRIEST_BLESSING_OF_THE_WAR_GOD">
		<sheet>
			<description><p>The Goddess of War and Hunt bestows upon you endurance and knowledge. You can choose one your proficient skills to make it expert.</p></description>
			<description level="9"><p>The Goddess of War and Hunt bestows upon you endurance and knowledge. You gain advantage of your Constitution saving throws and you can choose two your proficient skills to make it expert.</p></description>
			<description level="14"><p>The Goddess of War and Hunt bestows upon you endurance and knowledge. You gain advantage of your Constitution saving throws and you can choose three your proficient skills to make it expert.</p></description>
		</sheet>
		<rules>
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Blessing (War Priest)" level="6" number="1" supports="ID_INTERNAL_SUPPORT_EXPERTISE"/>
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Blessing (War Priest)" level="9" number="1" supports="ID_INTERNAL_SUPPORT_EXPERTISE"/>
			<select type="Class Feature" name="Blessing (War Priest)" level="14" number="1" supports="ID_INTERNAL_SUPPORT_EXPERTISE"/>
		</rules>
	</element>
	<!--Tamamlanmadı --><element name="Avatar of Battle" type="Class Feature" source="Player’s Handbook" id="ID_WOTC_PHB_CLASS_FEATURE_WAR_DOMAIN_AVATAR_OF_BATTLE">
		<requirements>!ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_WAR_DOMAIN_AVATAR_OF_BATTLE</requirements>
		<description>
			<p>At 17th level, you gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage from nonmagical attacks.</p>
		</description>
		<sheet>
			<description>You gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage from nonmagical attacks.</description>
		</sheet>
	</element>

	<!--Feature Replacement Grants-->
	<element name="Bonus Proficiencies Feature Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_WAR_DOMAIN_BONUS_PROFICIENCIES" />
	<element name="War Priest Feature Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_WAR_DOMAIN_WAR_PRIEST" />
	<element name="Channel Divinity: Guided Strike Feature Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_WAR_DOMAIN_CD_GUIDED_STRIKE" />
	<element name="Channel Divinity: War God’s Blessing Feature Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_WAR_DOMAIN_CD_WAR_GODS_BLESSING" />
	<element name="Avatar of Battle Feature Replacement" type="Grants" source="Internal" id="ID_INTERNAL_FEATURE_REPLACEMENT_CLERIC_WAR_DOMAIN_AVATAR_OF_BATTLE" />
</elements>
